let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"RESTORE command is used to",
		answer:" Restore files from disks made using the BACKUP command",
		options:[
			" Restore files which are deleted recently",
			" Restore files from disks made using the BACKUP command",
			" Restore files is used to",
			" Restore files from recycle bin"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"____ used to create a new Directory or nested Directories.",
		answer:"MD or MKDIR",
		options:[
			"MND or MKNDIR",
			" MZND or MKMDIR",
			"DM or MFDIR",
			"MD or MKDIR"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"While working with MS-DOS which command transfers a specific file from one disk to another?",
		answer:" Copy",
		options:[
			"  Copy",
			"Diskcopy",
			" Time",
			" Rename"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"Restarting a running computer is called",
		answer:"Warm boot",
		options:[
			"Normal boot",
			" Cold boot",
			"Cool boot",
			"Warm boot"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"Which of the following error will not be handled by the operating system?",
		answer:"Dust out from the system unit",
		options:[
			"Connection failure in the network",
			"Power failure",
			"Lack of paper in printer",
			"Dust out from the system unit"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"Copy and Xcopy are same in the sense",
		answer:"Both can be used to copy file or group of files",
		options:[
			"Both can be used to copy file or group of files",
			"Both are internal command of DOS",
			" Both are external commands of DOS",
			"Both a and b "
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"_____ command defines a list of directories DOS searches for external commands.",
		answer:"  PATH",
		options:[
			"TREE",
			"DSKCHK",
			" TREE",
			" PATH"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"What happens when you boot up a PC?",
		answer:"Portions of the operating system are copied from disk into memory",
		options:[
			"Portions of the operating system are copied from disk into memory",
			"Portions of the operating system are copied from memory onto disk",
			" Portions of the operating system are compiled",
			"Portions of the operating system are emulated"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"Which of the following(s) is/are the characteristic(s) of UNIX??",
		answer:"All of these",
		options:[
			"Multi user",
			"Multi tasking",
			"Kernel Manages data",
			"All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Which of the following is not an advantage of multiprogramming?",
		answer:"Decreased operating system overhead",
		options:[
			"Ability to assign priorities to jobs",
			"Decreased operating system overhead",
			"Shorter response time",
			"Increased throughout"
		]
	},
];